<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Alexandra Jardine]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Associate Creativity Editor ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Flexitime, Working from home and remote working]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[Working flexibly from home has enabled me to work for the past eight years at a job I enjoy, while at the same time being there for my children for everything that matters to them, from homework to sports days and play rehearsals (plus, not having to invest in extra childcare). This works very well for our family, as I have a husband who has a very full-on medical job and is rarely able to take time off or work flexibly. I don't think this would have been possible 20 years ago in my job as part of a team on a magazine, but technology means that I can file all my work remotely and talk to my work colleagues easily using Slack, email etc. even though they are in the US (and in fact, my direct boss also works from home in LA.) I also feel I am more productive working at home in a quiet study than I would be in an office. You do miss office banter and possibly the ability to bounce ideas around, but on the whole I think it enables you to focus and to concentrate on work without distractions - or office politics.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Alexandra_Jardine.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Amie Esson]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Senior Estimator ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Staggered hours, Working from home and remote working ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I considered going part time after my daughter was born, but technology and a culture of trust and openness at Willmott Dixon have enabled me to work flexibly and stay full time. Being able to start earlier and finish earlier means I have more time in the evenings to be with my family. It gives me a chance to catch up on my daughter's day before she goes to bed. Also working from home now and then allows me to drop my daughter off at Nursery so that I can be involved with her education and development too.I admit that I felt a little guilty about leaving early at first but after a few weeks it became the norm and now others in my office are starting to work similar patterns.I think agile and flexible working are moving in the right direction and that different ways of working are becoming more accepted in construction. Since my return there is now a structured return process in place that eases parents back into the work environment and culture. I believe more can be done in the way of peer support from other parents through potential parent networks.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Amie-Esson.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Andrea Mulligan ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Director New Business ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Working from home and remote working ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I joined R/GA, a digital innovation agency based in London, last year through a returnship initiative co-founded by the agency's HR Director, Liz Nottingham. The question of flexibility was discussed very openly during the interview process and on my suggestion, I started off working four days in the office and one half day from home with the flexibility to amend this pattern after an initial settling-in period.My feeling on flexibility has always been that one size definitely doesn't fit all. The different working patterns of the parents at my agency reflect this. In my view it takes time to find a pattern that works based upon the role, team, cadence of the working week and of course childcare commitments. I am hugely fortunate in that my husband often works from home and so is able to do school drop-offs and pick-ups certain days of a week. Childcare is very much a shared responsibility for us and the flexibility in his role complements that which I have in mine.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/AndreaMulligan.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Andrew Cooper]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Deputy Director Organisational Development and Design]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Compressed hours  ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[When our twin boys were born in 2001 we already had a daughter under the age of three and we needed to balance work and child care while considering the best arrangements for our children.Maternity leave was shorter then and my wife went back to work part time after 16 weeks. We took advantage of the 8am to 6pm nursery provision but felt we were missing out as our children developed and thoughts turned to me taking one day a week off work.I was working as a private secretary for a director general in the Department of Health, and at first I didn't think it would be possible.However, after discussion with the director general we agreed that I would take Mondays off but remain a full-time employee, so I worked longer days Tuesdays to Fridays.It was great to be able to take a day off to look after the children, though I sometimes felt guilty that colleagues were working when I was enjoying a sunny morning playing with the children in Battersea Park. That feeling soon passed.Back then very few men of my generation were out and about with young children. This has radically changed, which is surely a good thing, though clearly there is a long way to go.In my experience, my managers in the Civil Service have been more open to my request to work flexibly. It has always been a matter of negotiation and discussion in every one of my 10 different roles since starting working flexibly.I have gained two promotions and am now at deputy director level so it should not be a bar to progression, regardless of gender.Working flexibly at a senior level has been a really positive experience for me. It can only be a good thing for our health and wellbeing and something we should be proud of in PHE. It is good for us as individuals and reflects well on us as an employer.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Andrew-Cooper-.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Andy Rogers ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Global HR Director, Government & Agencies]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I shifted to working three days a week in February as my wife fell ill last summer and I have needed to spend time supporting her since then.   My change in working hours has coincided with a change in my role.  As a result, I have altered my approach and I am now able to plan my work commitments well in advance and review plans where travel is needed.  It has taken time to adapt to my new routine and I have found it easier to be clear about which days I work and which I do not, rather than change these around or operate on number of hours worked.  I work from Tuesday to Thursday and while I do look through emails on Monday and Friday, I try to keep everything at arm's length. On the days that I don't work, my attention is on my wife, allowing me to be more focussed on my working days. It has been challenging to adapt to not being available to colleagues on Monday and Friday, while working at 100% on the remaining days of the week.  However, having a supportive and pragmatic boss, as well as a flexible employer has helped me enormously to balance my personal and professional commitments.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Andy-Rogers.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Angela Chan ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Creative Diversity & Special Projects]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[In her role as Head of Creative Diversity, Angela leads a team with responsibility for ensuring Channel 4's programmes reflect the diversity of the audience, as well as advocating for more diversity in the creative industries as a whole. She and her colleagues work within the channel's creative commissioning team to find and break new onscreen talent, boost underrepresented talent within the industry and advise independent producers on getting diversity right.  She is also Head of Special Projects, using her experience in innovation and organisational change to deliver exciting new opportunities. Angela works four days per week in order to balance her career with her family and her studies. She is currently completing an Executive MBA with Ashridge Hult.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/ANGELA-CHAN.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Angus Crowther]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Founding Partner]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[So what flexible working means for me is that is has, frankly, changed my life. Having been part of the original Oystercatchers team from the start, it was incredibly stressful being a key member in a start-up with aggressive sales targets which in the end attracted a bid from Centaur Media.Now I have begun a new consultancy, Alchemists but I am still able to work 4 days a week which I agreed with my business partner, Vlad Komanicky, before we started up. This allows me to concentrate on my vineyard and family farm in North Essex, and have more time with my 4 children. Flexible working is the future. I am more efficient and effective now. At Alchemists we use tech to communicate more efficiently and can work on stuff together online. I never waste time. I get a lot more done. I earn more. Crucially I see my wife and kids a lot more, I am happier and less stressed.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Angus-headshot.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Anna Cook]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Director of Customer Service]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time, Flexitime]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[Back in 2013 I was returning from maternity leave, living in Newcastle, with a job that I loved in Sky in communications that was based in Scotland and London. I wanted to come back to work. I loved my job but had no clue how I could be a brilliant mum and be brilliant at work. My solution, which Sky fully supported, was part-time. Working 4 days a week but with flexibility so that I could be at work when I needed to be and still do some drop offs and pick-ups in Newcastle.And for me it has worked. Through two promotions, numerous home life changes (my son starting school, a critically ill parent) and shuffling of hours, I manage to balance a big, broad job with being around at home.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Anna-Cook.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Barbara Collins]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Women in Leadership]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Staggered hours]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[As a mother of four children, the ability to work flexibly has always been important, but this became critical when my youngest child left nursery and all my children were at school. I was fortunate enough to have a really enlightened manager - who was willing to think and act flexibly - and he agreed to a personalised flexible full-time working pattern, which enabled me to start work early in the morning (7:00) and leave in the afternoon to collect the children from school. We also agreed a back-up plan when occasional urgent afternoon work emerged, but the ability to pick issues up later in the evening largely solved any problems. This early-early arrangement worked for the family because my husband (who works for the Ministry of Justice) was able to negotiate a complementary late-late pattern and look after the children in the mornings. We all benefitted: my husband felt fully engaged with caring for the children; I have been able to support my children with their studies and after-school activities; and, the children (now in their twenties) never considered us to be working parents. This pattern wouldn't work for everyone and is ideally suited to couples. The early mornings are sometimes tough and the days are busy and long. Nevertheless, it has been rewarding to share the care and has enabled us both to progress in our careers. ]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Barbara-Collins.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Ben Shaw]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Industry]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Working from home and remote working]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I have been flexi-working since joining Sky in 2010. I normally work from home three days a week and spend the other two in Sky, I have two young children and working from home means I can walk my daughter to school in the morning and give my wife some much needed relief from the kids. She can go out and leave my young son with me or I can do the school pick up.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Ben-Shaw.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Caitlin Cockerton ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Director ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time, Annualised hours]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I've worked flexibly on two models for the last 18 months, following my return to work after having my daughter. The first model - 4 days a week, Monday to Thursday - enabled me to dive back into work in a nearly-full time capacity while keeping 1 day a week to have dedicated time with my child. In the 15 months I worked on this model, I accelerated my career and earned a promotion, which was great. I at times worked more than 4 days per week and probably didn't get the financial compensation for this 'extra time'. In my new role as a Director, I was keen to find a model that appreciated the true nature of our business - demanding full time work at times, but then also having some calmer periods. My new model is 180 days per year (equivalent to 3.5 days/week pro rata), worked flexibly - sometimes working 4 or 5 days a week when the demand is high, but also retaining the time I'm owed back, either by working 2 or 3 days some weeks, or by taking chunks of time off. This new model is an experiment for me and for the organisation and no one else at this level works on such a model so, we'll see how it goes!]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/CaitlinCockerton.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Caroline Wood]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Media]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Job share & Job split, Flexitime]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I returned to work after a two year break to focus on my children and it was harder than I'd anticipated. There was a real lack of options for my level, which offered any kind of flexibility, but then a job came up at Mencap, who are a very progressive employer.I found someone that I jelled with and we decided to job share - a completely new concept to me. It's great for employers as you effectively get two heads for the price of one. My job share partner and I work fixed days each week, but we have built in flexibility so that we can respond to business and personal needs when they arise.    She is currently on maternity leave so I am working full-time, but flexibly, so that two days a week I can pick my boys up from school. Full-time felt daunting at first, but Mencap genuinely puts the needs of its employees first, trusts them to be professionals and get the work done. That approach has made all the difference and I'm surprised more employers haven't cottoned on to the fact that a better work/life balance ultimately makes people more productive.You have to be very organised, but it's incredibly empowering and my team has adjusted well. They know that I am available if something crucial comes up, but they respect the time I need to spend with my children. As well as being more focused and efficient at work, it's been really positive for mine and my family's wellbeing. My husband and I didn't want to perpetuate old-fashioned gender stereotypes. We wanted our sons to grow up seeing us sharing parenting responsibilities alongside work, so that they experience gender equality as the social norm not the exception.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Caroline-Wood.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Catherine Chapman]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Legal Assessor & Trainer]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Working from home and remote working, Part time, flexitime]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I requested a four day working pattern - Monday to Thursday - which my employer agreed to, in line with their flexible working policy. I'm also home-based, as are most of my team colleagues, because we are located all over England. The nature of our work means that we can do our jobs effectively with just a laptop and phone. We have monthly team Skype calls and quarterly meetings at our head office or regional locations, which is a good opportunity to catch up.Although my job entails frequent visits to clients, I manage my own diary, so I can schedule visits to avoid rush hour. This makes for less stressful travelling, cheaper off-peak fares (a saving for my employer!) and just as important - I can often be back home in time for when my youngest son returns from school. I also value the fact that when I am at home, I can fit in some domestic chores,  and am much more efficient in getting things done, as there are fewer distractions, i.e. no one to chat to in the office!I probably wouldn't have chosen to work from home if I was younger and at the start of my career, because of the lack of social interaction, but now that my children are teenagers, this pattern suits me and our family life very well. ]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Catherine-Chapman.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Catherine Fry]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Compliance]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I have been working flexibly for the last few years in my role as Head of Compliance in the investment management industry.  I work part-time, but increased my core working hours from 3 days per week to 4 recently.  The children didn't need me around quite so much and I was able to take on some additional responsibilities.  More recently, I have changed my working pattern again, so that I work my 4 days across 5, and work one of those from home.  This has allowed me to respond to my children's immediate needs and acknowledges that, as they grow up, their needs can and will change.  We have always found a way to meet both my family's needs and my employers, and that is down to good communication between us.  My working environment is well organised, with meetings arranged well in advance which allows me to plan my working week to ensure that I am present when I need to be.  It helps that technology allows us to work remotely, so if anything urgent comes up I can still attend to it straight away.  Working a shorter day has been great for productivity.  Studies have shown that workers are not fully productive on a full working day so I feel my employer gains by me working additional shorter days rather than fewer longer ones.  My children get to see me when they come home from school too, and I feel I'm supporting them as a stay at home mum would.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Catherine-Fry.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Ceri Roberts]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Supplies People Manager]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Job share & Job split]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I started a formal job share in my role as Supplies People Manager in January 2016, although the first six months were undertaken as a trial to ensure that the arrangement worked for all parties involved. I remain highly motivated and engaged and I certainly have an increased sense of loyalty to the company for giving me this great opportunity. Sharing your role with someone means that you make a commitment to communicate and to trust!]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Ceri-Roberts.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Charlotte Budd]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Director]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[My husband and I share communications with the school so that it's not just one parent doing all the school admin.I'm on the class WhatsApp group and PTA facebook page which includes all info about social, extra-curricular and fundraising activities. My husband gets 'parent mail' which is the official communications channel of the school.We discuss and share what we learn but by dividing up the channels we both handle different parts of administration and can be more agile at work around parenting/school commitments.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Charlotte.Budd.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Chiazo Okey-Nzewuihe]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Surveyor]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Flexitime]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I start and finish early, working from 8.30am to 4pm as I have a long commute to the construction site in Twickenham where I am currently based. I can then log in from home later in the evening, depending on my workload. What sets Willmott Dixon apart from other construction firms, is its openness about different ways of working, as long as managers know what is going on they can try to deal with situations in everyone's interests. It is very motivating and makes for a happy workforce. Although I am aware that my work location will be subject to change - I have been based in Twickenham for just under a year - I know that Willmott Dixon will take employees' personal circumstances into account as much as possible when they move them around.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Chiazo-Okey-Nzewuihe.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Christine Smith ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Finance Business Partner]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Flexitime]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[We recently bought a new build house which should have been ready for the start of the new school year when my son moved to senior school. The house was delayed which meant we were living 20 miles away from my son's new school. I was able to work flexibly to pick him up after school and then I worked my hours later in the day from home. As a parent this was so important and as an employee of Greggs I cannot emphasise enough how this kind of flexibility and support is welcomed and appreciated.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/ChristineSmith.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Clare Ely and Jane Beacon ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Daytime]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Job share & Job split]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[Clare and Jane are jointly responsible for over 3,000 hours of television a year, including Good Morning Britain, Loose Women, Tipping Point and The Chase. Their role involves commissioning new shows as well as ensuring that long-running favourites continue to captivate their audiences. Clare and Jane have worked together for 25 years, and have previously produced flagships shows including Dancing on Ice and This Morning. They joined ITV as Commissioning Editor as a jobshare partnership and were promoted to Head of Daytime with the same arrangement. Between them, they have four young children, and chose to work fewer hours in order to maximise the time they can spend with their growing families. ]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Clare-Ely-and-Jane-Beacon.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Daniel Feeney ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Visitor Services, Buckingham Palace]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Compressed hours]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[After my wife returned to work in a senior role with the National Trust we both made the call to take the same flexible working steps, condensing our hours into 4 days so that each of us gets one full day with our son and the full weekend together as a family. We're 6 months into it now and it certainly feels like it is working, and indeed we think he is benefitting from having the three days at nursery too in the middle of the week. From a personal perspective, I know that I am benefitting from having a day of dedicated Father and Son time, and am more motivated when in the office knowing that I have an employer who understands how important my role as a Father is to me.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Daniel-Feeney.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[David ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Business Analyst ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I recently paid off my mortgage, and with both of my sons now grown up and able to look after themselves, I decided to reduce my working days from 5 to 4 to give me more time to pursue other interests. The key to making this work is to stay flexible. A simple swap of a non-working day can be needed if you have to attend an important meeting. I did wonder if people would see a reduction of work hours negatively, but this hasn't happened. I am now happier and more motivated.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/David_Rank.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Elizabeth Bailey ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Working from home and remote working]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I've been extremely impressed at Barclays' approach and commitment to Dynamic Working, and in return it's meant I'm highly motivated and committed to Barclays for the long term.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Faith Pullen ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[European Financial Planning &amp; Analysis Manager]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time, Term-time working & full-time part year ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[Over the years I have used; part time hours, flexible hours, a sabbatical and term time working. Currently I work 22.5 hours per week; 2 standard days and 2 short school hour days, with flexibility over which days these are, along with 4 weeks extended parental leave in the school summer holidays.  Of course there are occasions when I need to flex and catch up things later, but all my colleagues and managers are very supportive.  When I'm working I'm able to fully commit without guilt, and thrive on the different challenges of my work versus personal role. An unexpected benefit of flexible working has been strengthening of skill set, it has focused development of prioritization, decision making, communication and delegation.  Supporting such a flexible working pattern and supporting me to take time away on sabbatical whilst a bold and brave move for Mars, is also common across the business, and has also required me to take some risks and be flexible on the career path I've taken but I've been lucky that the people and company have let me demonstrate that this works across a number of roles; UK, Global and European, both within my area of expertise and encouraging me to grow and develop in a new function and to maintain a successful career path.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Faith-Pullen.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
</data>
