<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Alexandra Jardine]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Associate Creativity Editor ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Flexitime, Working from home and remote working]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[Working flexibly from home has enabled me to work for the past eight years at a job I enjoy, while at the same time being there for my children for everything that matters to them, from homework to sports days and play rehearsals (plus, not having to invest in extra childcare). This works very well for our family, as I have a husband who has a very full-on medical job and is rarely able to take time off or work flexibly. I don't think this would have been possible 20 years ago in my job as part of a team on a magazine, but technology means that I can file all my work remotely and talk to my work colleagues easily using Slack, email etc. even though they are in the US (and in fact, my direct boss also works from home in LA.) I also feel I am more productive working at home in a quiet study than I would be in an office. You do miss office banter and possibly the ability to bounce ideas around, but on the whole I think it enables you to focus and to concentrate on work without distractions - or office politics.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Alexandra_Jardine.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Amie Esson]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Senior Estimator ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Staggered hours, Working from home and remote working ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I considered going part time after my daughter was born, but technology and a culture of trust and openness at Willmott Dixon have enabled me to work flexibly and stay full time. Being able to start earlier and finish earlier means I have more time in the evenings to be with my family. It gives me a chance to catch up on my daughter's day before she goes to bed. Also working from home now and then allows me to drop my daughter off at Nursery so that I can be involved with her education and development too.I admit that I felt a little guilty about leaving early at first but after a few weeks it became the norm and now others in my office are starting to work similar patterns.I think agile and flexible working are moving in the right direction and that different ways of working are becoming more accepted in construction. Since my return there is now a structured return process in place that eases parents back into the work environment and culture. I believe more can be done in the way of peer support from other parents through potential parent networks.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Amie-Esson.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Andrea Mulligan ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Director New Business ]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Working from home and remote working ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I joined R/GA, a digital innovation agency based in London, last year through a returnship initiative co-founded by the agency's HR Director, Liz Nottingham. The question of flexibility was discussed very openly during the interview process and on my suggestion, I started off working four days in the office and one half day from home with the flexibility to amend this pattern after an initial settling-in period.My feeling on flexibility has always been that one size definitely doesn't fit all. The different working patterns of the parents at my agency reflect this. In my view it takes time to find a pattern that works based upon the role, team, cadence of the working week and of course childcare commitments. I am hugely fortunate in that my husband often works from home and so is able to do school drop-offs and pick-ups certain days of a week. Childcare is very much a shared responsibility for us and the flexibility in his role complements that which I have in mine.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/AndreaMulligan.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Andrew Cooper]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Deputy Director Organisational Development and Design]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Compressed hours  ]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[When our twin boys were born in 2001 we already had a daughter under the age of three and we needed to balance work and child care while considering the best arrangements for our children.Maternity leave was shorter then and my wife went back to work part time after 16 weeks. We took advantage of the 8am to 6pm nursery provision but felt we were missing out as our children developed and thoughts turned to me taking one day a week off work.I was working as a private secretary for a director general in the Department of Health, and at first I didn't think it would be possible.However, after discussion with the director general we agreed that I would take Mondays off but remain a full-time employee, so I worked longer days Tuesdays to Fridays.It was great to be able to take a day off to look after the children, though I sometimes felt guilty that colleagues were working when I was enjoying a sunny morning playing with the children in Battersea Park. That feeling soon passed.Back then very few men of my generation were out and about with young children. This has radically changed, which is surely a good thing, though clearly there is a long way to go.In my experience, my managers in the Civil Service have been more open to my request to work flexibly. It has always been a matter of negotiation and discussion in every one of my 10 different roles since starting working flexibly.I have gained two promotions and am now at deputy director level so it should not be a bar to progression, regardless of gender.Working flexibly at a senior level has been a really positive experience for me. It can only be a good thing for our health and wellbeing and something we should be proud of in PHE. It is good for us as individuals and reflects well on us as an employer.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Andrew-Cooper-.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Andy Rogers ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Global HR Director, Government & Agencies]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[I shifted to working three days a week in February as my wife fell ill last summer and I have needed to spend time supporting her since then.   My change in working hours has coincided with a change in my role.  As a result, I have altered my approach and I am now able to plan my work commitments well in advance and review plans where travel is needed.  It has taken time to adapt to my new routine and I have found it easier to be clear about which days I work and which I do not, rather than change these around or operate on number of hours worked.  I work from Tuesday to Thursday and while I do look through emails on Monday and Friday, I try to keep everything at arm's length. On the days that I don't work, my attention is on my wife, allowing me to be more focussed on my working days. It has been challenging to adapt to not being available to colleagues on Monday and Friday, while working at 100% on the remaining days of the week.  However, having a supportive and pragmatic boss, as well as a flexible employer has helped me enormously to balance my personal and professional commitments.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Andy-Rogers.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Angela Chan ]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Creative Diversity & Special Projects]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[In her role as Head of Creative Diversity, Angela leads a team with responsibility for ensuring Channel 4's programmes reflect the diversity of the audience, as well as advocating for more diversity in the creative industries as a whole. She and her colleagues work within the channel's creative commissioning team to find and break new onscreen talent, boost underrepresented talent within the industry and advise independent producers on getting diversity right.  She is also Head of Special Projects, using her experience in innovation and organisational change to deliver exciting new opportunities. Angela works four days per week in order to balance her career with her family and her studies. She is currently completing an Executive MBA with Ashridge Hult.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/ANGELA-CHAN.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Angus Crowther]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Founding Partner]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[So what flexible working means for me is that is has, frankly, changed my life. Having been part of the original Oystercatchers team from the start, it was incredibly stressful being a key member in a start-up with aggressive sales targets which in the end attracted a bid from Centaur Media.Now I have begun a new consultancy, Alchemists but I am still able to work 4 days a week which I agreed with my business partner, Vlad Komanicky, before we started up. This allows me to concentrate on my vineyard and family farm in North Essex, and have more time with my 4 children. Flexible working is the future. I am more efficient and effective now. At Alchemists we use tech to communicate more efficiently and can work on stuff together online. I never waste time. I get a lot more done. I earn more. Crucially I see my wife and kids a lot more, I am happier and less stressed.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Angus-headshot.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Anna Cook]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Director of Customer Service]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Part time, Flexitime]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[Back in 2013 I was returning from maternity leave, living in Newcastle, with a job that I loved in Sky in communications that was based in Scotland and London. I wanted to come back to work. I loved my job but had no clue how I could be a brilliant mum and be brilliant at work. My solution, which Sky fully supported, was part-time. Working 4 days a week but with flexibility so that I could be at work when I needed to be and still do some drop offs and pick-ups in Newcastle.And for me it has worked. Through two promotions, numerous home life changes (my son starting school, a critically ill parent) and shuffling of hours, I manage to balance a big, broad job with being around at home.]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Anna-Cook.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Barbara Collins]]></name>
		<jobtitle><![CDATA[Head of Women in Leadership]]></jobtitle>
		<work><![CDATA[Staggered hours]]></work>
		<content><![CDATA[As a mother of four children, the ability to work flexibly has always been important, but this became critical when my youngest child left nursery and all my children were at school. I was fortunate enough to have a really enlightened manager - who was willing to think and act flexibly - and he agreed to a personalised flexible full-time working pattern, which enabled me to start work early in the morning (7:00) and leave in the afternoon to collect the children from school. We also agreed a back-up plan when occasional urgent afternoon work emerged, but the ability to pick issues up later in the evening largely solved any problems. This early-early arrangement worked for the family because my husband (who works for the Ministry of Justice) was able to negotiate a complementary late-late pattern and look after the children in the mornings. We all benefitted: my husband felt fully engaged with caring for the children; I have been able to support my children with their studies and after-school activities; and, the children (now in their twenties) never considered us to be working parents. This pattern wouldn't work for everyone and is ideally suited to couples. The early mornings are sometimes tough and the days are busy and long. Nevertheless, it has been rewarding to share the care and has enabled us both to progress in our careers. ]]></content>
		<link><![CDATA[/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Barbara-Collins.jpg]]></link>
	</node>
</data>
